[Music]
Welcome back. You're watching us here on
Bazar Morning Call. A 40 point uptake on
the gift nifty after a good 180 point
rally on the nifty yesterday. A bunch of
stocks doing well. In fact, 1,800 stocks
in the green for about 1,000 stocks in
the red yesterday which were the big
movers which saw healthy volumes. We
have Hormas with the delivery data.
Hormas.
>> Good morning, Mangala. and Urban Company
is the first one that comes to mind
because it's after after the big listing
pop that it saw. The stock just fell off
the radar and then sprung up yesterday
among the list of gainers. It was the
second best performance for the stock in
its brief trading history since its
listing day is the first instance after
the last nine sessions that more than 1
cr shares were traded on the stock
yesterday. Well over 3 cr shares were
bid for and 42 lakh of those were marked
for delivery. mentioning this stock
today as well because the one month
shareholder lockin period ends today and
as a result of the move that it saw
yesterday that 11% up move the stock
closed above its listing price of 162
which it had fallen below as a result of
that 5-day losing streak that it had
seen before yesterday's up move PSU
banks led the charge yesterday as well
as the continuing with their
outperformance and bank of Maharashtra
was among the top movers in that pack
almost 8% higher the biggest single day
gain in well over a year volumes also
were the highest in well over a year The
were almost 10 crore shares were traded
on Bank of Maharashtra yesterday. The
20-day average here is just over a cr
of those were marked for delivery. The
20-day average here is just around 55
lakh shares. The two earnings reactions
that stood out yesterday. One was ICICI
Lombard. The other one being persistent
systems. Both of them ending with gains
of anywhere up to 9%. And look at the
volumes here as well. Almost 70 lakh
shares for ICICI Lombard. 35 lakh for
persistent systems. And that is at least
15 10 to 15 times higher than their
respective 20-day average. And you take
a look at the delivery volumes as well.
ICIC Lombard had almost 11 lakh shares
marked for delivery. Persistent had
close to 19 lakh shares marked for
delivery. So strong delivery based
buying in these earnings reactions as
well. And lastly, GM breweries, we spoke
about this on closing. You added to it
as well. And the trading look at the
trading volumes here. Uh from the start
of the year until the 8th of October,
the average daily traded volume in GM
breweries was just 75,000 shares. It
reported its results and ever since then
the average daily traded volume has been
55 lakh shares for GM breweries. Even
yesterday we had 1.1 cr shares that were
traded on the stock. The 20-day average
here is just 11 lakh shares and this two
is because of this last 3 four days
where there has been extended trading
activity and out of that 1.1 cr shares 6
and a half lakh were marked for
delivery. The 20-day average here is
just over a lakh. That's GM breweries
for you up almost 60% now in the last 10
sessions.
>> Yes. And when you said you added to it,
I meant added to it on the research side
and not perhaps on the consumption side
out there.